<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>🪴 The Wizard's keep on</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/</link><description>Recent content in 🪴 The Wizard's keep on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aldactone</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Aldactone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Aldactone/</guid><description>Go back to the Compounds coridor Go back to the castle entrerance Aldactone Class: Diuretic (potassium sparing) Form: Oral Dosage unit: milligrams
Videos Complete guide to pharmaceutical diuretics Peak Week - Timing Diuretics Aldactone in 60 seconds Application Diuretic Warning ⚠️ - Potential of high potassium blood levels if abused
Prerequisites Usage Pre-contest Goes well with</description></item><item><title>Amphitheater</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Amphitheater/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Amphitheater/</guid><description>Go back to the castle entrance Amphitheater entrance As you walk from the main hall towards a set of handsome highly polished double oak doors, surrounding sounds seem to dampen. Your footsteps are nearly soundless and the walls seem to absorb every noise from the surrounding air.
The doors open with only a light touch and swing open soundlessly. Smells of popcorn and carpeted floors confirm to you you&amp;rsquo;re in the right place.</description></item><item><title>Compounds corridor</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Compounds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Compounds/</guid><description>Go back to the castle entrance Compounds corridor As you walk up the stairs you come to a corridor with an odd smell. Odors and colored clouds seem to drift and mingle in the air, sometimes fusing with a small crackle of anabolic potential and alchemical bliss.
At the top of the stairs a plaque on the wall reads:
The poison is in the dose! Be the alchemist of your own chemistry</description></item><item><title>Crossfit</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Crossfit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Crossfit/</guid><description>Go back to the Sport and subject specific information hallway Go back to the castle entrance The CrossFit Corridor The hallway fills with the smell of ruber tiled floors, sweaty (often shirtless) high fiving men and woman, rusty barbells with bumper plates and some serious athletic potential.
Video&amp;rsquo;s, Q&amp;amp;A&amp;rsquo;s, nutrition, PED&amp;rsquo;s, all related to the sport of CrossFit.
Moving paintings (video&amp;rsquo;s) On the wall there are several moving paintings with small plaques beneath them describing their content.</description></item><item><title>Female Athletics</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Female-Athletics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Female-Athletics/</guid><description> Go back to the Sport and subject specific information hallway Go back to the castle entrance Female Athletics Corridor Post 15-11-2021 - Female PED Basics</description></item><item><title>MT2</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Compounds/MT2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Compounds/MT2/</guid><description>Go back to the castle entrance Go back to the Compounds corridor
Melanotan 2 Class: Peptide Form: Injectable Dosage unit: micrograms
Application Tanning Increases [[insulin sensitivity]] Libido and [[sexuality functionality]] Phlebotomy / Blood prolifirators &amp;gt;- Increases ability to transport oxygen around the body Global/systemic stimulation of fat cell apoptosis Warning ⚠️ - If ran unchecked can increase risk of blood clotting / stroke / etc</description></item><item><title>Physique based Athletics</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Physique-based-athletics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Physique-based-athletics/</guid><description>Go back to the sport and subject specific information corridor Go back to the castle entrance Physique based athletics A corridor full of doors, each labeled with a neat plaque set above the door. Multiple mirrors are positioned so one can see oneself from any angle while walking this hallway!
A plaque at the top of the stairs reads:
&amp;ldquo;Not now chief! I&amp;rsquo;m in the fucking zone..!&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Post_partum_recovery</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Posts/Post-partum-recovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Posts/Post-partum-recovery/</guid><description>Go back to the Pregnancy, Gestation &amp;amp; Post partum corridor Go back to the castle entrance Post partum recovery Introduction In the past I had always helped women randomly throughout their pregnancy or post partum phases and was even privileged enough to be brought in late in the gestational process to help with end of term mother and fetus health/development in preparation for the big day! Then I had 2 kids and this process became so interesting to me that I spent WAY too many hours reading as much as I could and paying gestational, lactation, and pregnancy experts to have consult calls with myself purely for the sake of education.</description></item><item><title>Powerlifting &amp; Strongman</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Powerlifting-Strongman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Powerlifting-Strongman/</guid><description> Go back to the Sport and subject specific information hallway Go back to the castle entrance</description></item><item><title>Pregnancy, Gestation &amp; Post partum</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Pregnancy-Gestation-Post-partum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Pregnancy-Gestation-Post-partum/</guid><description>Go back to the Sport and subject specific information hallway Go back to the castle entrance The Pregnancy, Gestation &amp;amp; Post partum corridor Close to the kitchens the corridor fills with the delicious smells of freshly baked goods, cinnamon, cardemon, butter, etc. The clean polished rosewood floors are inlaid with gold symbols representing male, female and everything in between.
Depicted on the walls are beautifully paintings of both food and (semi-)naked athletic bodies, a weird but odly satisfying combination that simply shouts potential fertility and procreation.</description></item><item><title>Q and A - September 2021</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/QndA-September2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/QndA-September2021/</guid><description>Go back to QandAs entrance.
Vimeo link: September 2021 - Q&amp;amp;A&amp;rsquo;s [Timestamp: 00:14] Question: Do you notice much difference between Pharma and ugl hgh?
[Timestamp: 00:40] Question: Do you see any negative outcomes on Hypertrophy, if Metformin is/isnt used on a daily basis?
etc etc etc</description></item><item><title>Q&amp;A's</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/QandAs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/QandAs/</guid><description>Go back up to the castle entrance You decend into a dark hallway, lit by only a few torches casting an eerie blue-ish light. The shadows cast by these torches are darker than they should be, you swear you can see your shadow move just slightly out of the cornor of your eye, yet you remained stock still.
The air is freezing cold, breath coming out in clouds and sparkling in the faint blue light before seeming to solidify in crystals upon the floor and walls.</description></item><item><title>Sport and subject specific information</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/sport-and-subject-specific-information/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/sport-and-subject-specific-information/</guid><description> Go back to the castle entrance Welcome to the first floor, sport and subject specific coridors branch from this main one. The coridor is brightly lit by stained glass windows set every few yards. There is a faint smell of ozone in the air, as though the potential that flows from the these branched halls is almost palpable.
Crossfit Powerlifting &amp;amp; Strongman Pregnancy, Gestation &amp;amp; Post partum Female Athletics Lacrosse Physique based athletics</description></item><item><title>Supplements</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Supplements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Supplements/</guid><description> Go back to the castle entrance</description></item><item><title>Testosterone</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Testosterone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Testosterone/</guid><description>Go back to the Compounds corridor
Go back to the castle entrance Compound: Testosterone Form: Injectable Type: Base androgen Use: General blanket androgen coverage
etc. etc. etc. etc.</description></item><item><title>Thyroid timing</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Thyroid-timing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Thyroid-timing/</guid><description> Go back to the castle entrance Thyroid medication timing Page with information about why your doctor is wrong perscribing thyroids meds in the morning!
information for noobs tyope something fun here..
Warning ⚠️ - If ran unchecked can increase risk of blood clotting / stroke / etc
Testosterone</description></item><item><title>Training</title><link>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pointfirestorm.github.io/quartz/Training/</guid><description> Go back to the castle entrance</description></item></channel></rss>